buyerzone.com 2016-12-22

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to www.buyerzone.com (the "Site") owned and operated by BuyerZone.com, LLC.

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy describes the information we gather, how we share that information and what we do to protect your information on our Site. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personally identifiable information and how you can access and update this information.

Use of the Site indicates agreement with this privacy policy. This privacy policy was last updated March 1, 2016.

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website www.buyerzone.com and does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software.

In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

### What Information Do We Gather?

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include, among other things, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data and device type. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality.

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts may be used by us and our partners, including affiliates, analytics or service providers, advertisers, and sellers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, optimizing the services we bring you, administering the Site, tracking users’ movements around the Site and to gathering demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

Cookies contain specific pieces of information on your computer hard drive, and can be set to store information during a visit or for a longer period of time. Cookies are also used to help streamline your experience on the Site, automatically logging you in during future visits, for example. You are free to disable cookies at any time if your browser permits. However, by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features of our Site. If you are unable to submit a Request for Quotes while having cookies disabled, please contact our Customer Care department at 888-393-5000.

The use of cookies by our partners, including affiliates, analytics or service providers, advertisers, and sellers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. 

We may use local storage objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information in order to embed videos on our website and to track usage of our videos. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our Site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity may use Flash cookies or HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>.

As a prospective buyer using offerings on our Site (such as our Request for Quotes service) to receive information from or about sellers, you are required to provide additional information so we can deliver these services to you. This includes contact information, such as name, title, company, address, phone number and email address, basic demographic information, and your purchasing requirements. The information collected varies according to the different purchasing categories and can be viewed by visiting the different forms located throughout our Site. We may also ask you for feedback about our service, which is collected and stored to allow us to continually improve our offerings.

As a supplier using offerings on our Site (such as our Request for Quotes service to receive information from or about prospective buyers), you must provide information that allows us to deliver our service to you. This includes your contact information, information about your desired target markets, and billing information.

We also require you to provide certain information such as name and email address when you request our newsletters, sample lead service or other content or submit information for posting on public areas of this site (e.g., blogs, moderated discussions or bulletin boards). Additionally, we may request that you provide demographic information. The specific information requested varies according to the different types of content you may request.

Some of the materials included on this Site, including advertising, may be served by third parties. These third parties, in the course of serving such materials, may collect information regarding your use of this Site and how you respond to e-mail communications, using methods that may include automatic data collection, and may use this information in order to present advertisements or other content that may be of interest to you on both this Site and other web sites. Collection, use, disclosure and security of information collected by third parties are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having this information used by certain third-party ad servers to provide targeted ads, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. 

### How Do We Use Your Information?

We use the information we gather to put buyers and sellers into contact with one another, to provide other features and functionality of this Site, to improve your experience on our Site through analysis and communication, for other purposes described in this policy, and for purposes disclosed to you when you provide information.

**To Facilitate Transactions.** Buyers or suppliers will receive emails and other communications from us to fulfill or facilitate the purpose for which the information was provided or a request to use a service on this site. You cannot opt out of emails that are necessary to provide our services. By using the services offered on this Site, you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information to contact you and deliver information to you related to those services. 

**Analysis.** In our ongoing effort to improve the content and services we offer, we continually analyze the information we receive to identify trends and patterns in user behavior. Your personally identifiable information, when used in such a manner, is aggregated with others to amass enough data for such analysis and is not personally identifiable. 

**Testimonials and Feedback.** We sincerely appreciate the feedback we receive from our users. We, and our service providers, may use your contact information to ask for feedback. Your feedback, both positive and negative, is forwarded to the appropriate departments at BuyerZone as necessary so we can continue to monitor and improve the service we provide. We may also share testimonials in our marketing literature and will display the name you use when registering for the feedback service on the feedback service’s website. If you would like your testimonial removed, please contact us at [privacy@buyerzone.com](mailto:privacy@buyerzone.com).

**Newsletters.** We offer valuable content through email newsletters for both buyers and suppliers. If you no longer wish to receive any newsletter, we encourage you to opt out of these communications by changing your notification preferences as described below. 

**Other communications.** We may send you email and other communications related to this Site, your use of our services and the status of your account, which may include Site updates and responses to your inquiries. In addition, we send periodic surveys and other communications, all of which you can opt out of receiving by changing your notification preferences as described below. 

**Affiliates.** We may share your information with our parent company, Purch Group, Inc. ("Purch"), and our affiliates owned or controlled in whole or in part by Purch, so they may engage in any uses that we may engage in as disclosed in this privacy policy. We or our affiliates may use the information you provide us to send you email and other communications on behalf of other Purch affiliates. These communications may include email newsletters, as well as offers for other BuyerZone and Purch services. All email newsletters will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of receiving future issues of the newsletter. All promotional offers will include an opportunity to opt out of receiving future promotions from the brand whose product/service is being promoted. 

**Third Party Offers.** We also may use your information to send you e-mail and other communications on behalf of third parties. Each of these communications will include instructions for opting out of receiving future third party offers from us. You may also opt out of receiving third party offers from this Site at any time by sending an e-mail to [privacy@buyerzone.com](mailto:privacy@buyerzone.com) with the subject line **"opt out — third party."**

### How Do We Share Your Information With Others?

Our customer information is an important part of our business. As a result, we only disclose this information as described in this section. Our sharing of information to outside parties is described below. As part of our service to customers, we provide information to suppliers so that they can respond directly to you when you submit a Request for Quotes. Information customers provide to a third party, such as by registering for a third party’s services or making a purchase, is not covered by this privacy policy.

**Prospective Buyers.** To facilitate our business of matching buyers and suppliers, prospective buyers using our services will be provided information about suppliers relevant to the buyer's request or inquiry using such services. This includes supplier contact information, company background information and, where appropriate, ratings or reviews. 

**Suppliers.** Similarly, suppliers whose products or services are relevant to a prospective buyer's request, and/or marketers, resellers and other service providers performing marketing, fulfillment and/or similar services on behalf of such suppliers with respect to the prospective buyer's request, may be provided with that prospective buyer's information. We contractually limit use of the buyer's information (including all forms of contact information submitted) by the seller to communicating with the buyer, or permitting its marketers, resellers or other service providers to communicate with the buyer, about their desired purchase. In addition, suppliers may receive information about buyers in a manner that does not disclose personally identifiable information. Examples include data that are aggregated across a group of buyers or feedback that is provided without attribution to a specific person or company. 

**Agents.** From time to time, we may use the services of third-party companies to help facilitate our business activities. These include bill collection services, affiliate or incentive program providers, customer service organizations, e-mail and postal mail brokers, and marketing service providers. These companies are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and are prohibited from using the information we provide for any reason except to perform the functions that we have outlined for them. 

**Network Members.** We have relationships with third parties to provide our services more broadly throughout the Internet to both buyers and suppliers. When a user has utilized these services through a member of our network, we will share information about these users with the affiliate as necessary. This information is typically reported in an aggregated format. 

**Advertisers.** We may provide your information to third party advertisers (and/or to their service providers on their behalf) to market their products or services under contractual requirement to keep your personally identifiable information confidential and use it only to market and provide (directly and through third parties engaged by them for such purpose) their products or services. You may opt out of such disclosures by sending an e-mail to [privacy@buyerzone.com](mailto:privacy@buyerzone.com) with the subject line: **"Do not disclose."** We also aggregate information about our collective users for potential advertisers who are interested in understanding whether their offering would be suitable to our audience. This information does not include personally identifiable information like your company name or email address. 

**Business Transitions.** As we continue to develop our business, we may buy, merge or partner with other companies. If that happens, we may acquire customer information. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. Similarly, if a portion or all of Purch’s assets are sold or transferred to a third-party, customer information (including your email address) would likely be one of the transferred business assets. You will receive notice as described in the "Notification of Changes" section below of any change in uses of your personally identifiable information, and choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information. 

**Law Enforcement and Legal Process.** We may report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we believe to be unlawful. We may also report any activities that we believe may aid a law enforcement investigation into unlawful activity. We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as we reasonably believe is necessary, in our sole judgment, to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect the rights, property or safety, of BuyerZone, its parent company, the public, or another user. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention. 

**Sharing Your Information as Permitted by Law.** We may share your information with others as required by law. We may also share your information with others as permitted by law. This may include sharing your information with government entities or third-parties in response to subpoenas, court orders, bankruptcy proceedings, other legal process. We may also share your information if we believe it is necessary to exercise our legal rights, to defend against legal claims that have been brought against us, or to defend against possible legal claims that we determine might be brought against us. 

###  How We Secure Personal Information

We take reasonable and appropriate measures to help keep information secure and to help prevent it from becoming disclosed to individuals who are not described in this policy. Even though we follow reasonable procedures to try to protect the information in our possession, no security system is perfect, and we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your information will be secure in all circumstances. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

Your account information will be protected by a password for your privacy and security, but we also recommend that you change your password periodically. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your account username and password. You may not provide these account credentials to any third party. If you believe that your account username and/or password have been stolen or been made known to others, you must contact us immediately at [privacy@buyerzone.com](mailto:privacy@buyerzone.com) and change your password immediately via our website. We are not responsible if someone else accesses your Account through information that they have obtained from you. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at [privacy@buyerzone.com](mailto:privacy@buyerzone.com) or by telephone or postal mail using the contact information below.

### Account Information and Preferences

BuyerZone.com provides a number of ways for you to manage your personally identifiable information.

**Account information.** If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, or if you need to update or delete your account information, such as your contact email address, you may do so by contacting our Customer Care department at [privacy@buyerzone.com](mailto:privacy@buyerzone.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

**Notification Preferences.** You have the ability to "opt out" or unsubscribe from certain e-mail communications, such as periodic surveys and our monthly email newsletter, that are not related to a requested service and/or the status of your account. To update your communication preferences, contact our Customer Care department at [privacy@buyerzone.com](mailto:privacy@buyerzone.com). If you do contact the Customer Care department, please be sure to specify the type of email communication(s) from which you would like to opt out. Information about how to unsubscribe is also included in every communication we send. 

**Password.** Our suppliers may be issued a User ID and password to access their account. As a supplier, you are responsible for all actions taken with your user ID and password, including fees charged to your account. Do not share your password with any third parties, as you may be legally liable for any fees that are incurred. If you believe that your password has been compromised, you should immediately change your password or contact Customer Care at [privacy@buyerzone.com](mailto:privacy@buyerzone.com) or 888-393-5000.

**Data Retention.** We will retain your information to continue to offer you products and services. Please contact us if you wish to cancel or request that we no longer use your information this way. We will also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

### Children

We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If it is discovered that we have collected personally identifiable information from someone under 13 we will delete that information immediately. Persons under the age of 18 are not eligible to use our services.

### Widgets

Our Site includes Widgets and social media features such as the Facebook "Like" button, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc.). Personally identifiable information, such as your email address, may be collected through these features. These features may collect your IP address and set cookies to enable them to function properly. Information collected by these features is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created the feature.

### Public Forums

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our blog or community forum, please contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### Legal Disclaimer

Although we have attempted to address the various privacy-related issues you are likely to encounter, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this privacy policy. Therefore, although we use standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private from unauthorized access.

Also, this Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site.

### Notification of Change

We may amend this privacy policy for minor changes at any time by posting the amended terms on the Site. All minor amended terms shall be effective upon posting. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by email or by posting a prominent notice for 30 days prior to the change taking effect.

### Your California Privacy Rights

We will provide individuals who are California residents a description of the categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. We will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like this information, please submit a written request to [privacy@buyerzone.com](mailto:privacy@buyerzone.com) or to BuyerZone.com at the mailing address below. In your request, please specify that you want a "California Privacy Rights Notice." Please allow 30 days for a response. 

### Contacting Us

If you have any additional questions or comments about this Site’s privacy statement, please contact us:

BuyerZone.com, LLC   
225 Wyman Street  
Waltham, MA 02451
